liasophia.com 2016-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Outlet by lia sophia

_Last Updated: June 22, 2016_

K-Five LLC, d/b/a Outlet by Lia Sophia (“Lia Sophia,” “we” or “us”) values your privacy. In this Privacy Policy (“Policy”), we describe how we collect, use, and disclose information that we obtain about visitors to our website [www.liasophia.com](http://www.liasophia.com/) (the “Site”) and users of the services available through our Site (collectively, the “Services”).

By visiting the Site, or using any of our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Policy. Your use of our Site or Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. The Lia Sophia Terms of Use are incorporated by reference into this Policy.

**What Information Do We Collect About You and Why?**

We may collect information about you directly from you and from third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site or Services.

_**Information We Collect Directly From You.**_ Certain areas and features of our Site and Services require registration. To register you must provide your name, email address and create a password. In addition, if you make a purchase, we will also request that you provide your credit or debit card information and your billing and shipping address. We also may collect additional information from you, including your birthday and preferences. You are not required to provide us with this information.

_**Information We Collect Automatically.**_ We may automatically collect the following information about your use of our Site or Services through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies: your domain name; your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; the length of time you visit our Site and or use our Services; and the referring URL, or the webpage that led you to our Site, and the following: access time, browser type, device ID, domain name, IP address, page views and referring URL. We may combine this information with other information that we have collected about you, including, where applicable, your user name, name, and other personal information please see the section “Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms” below for more information.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use your information, including your personal information, for the following purposes:

To provide our Services to you, to communicate with you about your use of our Services, to respond to your inquiries, to fulfill your orders, and for other customer service purposes.

To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Site or our Services.

For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we may use your information, such as your email address, to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you. We also may use the information that we learn about you to assist us in advertising our Services on third party websites.

To better understand how users access and use our Site and Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, in order to improve our Site and Services and respond to user desires and preferences, and for other research and analytical purposes.

To administer our customer loyalty program.

For other purposes related to the administration of our business, including to: (i) to maintain accurate customer and user records; (ii) monitor your compliance with any of your agreements with us; (iii) protect us, yourself and others from fraud and error and to safeguard our business interests; (iv) collect debts owed to us; and (v) comply with legal and regulatory requirements.

To manage or transfer our assets or liabilities, for example, in the case of an acquisition or merger of our business (in which case your information may be disclosed to potential purchasers), the provision of security for a credit facility or the change of a supplier of products or services.

For other purposes where authorized or required by law or consented to by you.

**How We Share Your Information**

We may share your information, including personal information, as follows:

_**Site Users**_ _._ Your user name and any information that you post to our Site, such as reviews, will be available to, and searchable by, all users of the Site and Services.

_**Affiliates**_. We may disclose the information we collect from you to our affiliates or subsidiaries; however, if we do so, their use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information will be subject to this Policy.

_**Marketing Partners.**_ We may also share your information with select business or marketing partners, who may contact you about information, products or services that you may be interested in.

_**Service Providers**_. We may disclose the information we collect from you to third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform functions on our behalf.

_**Business Transfers**_. If we are acquired by or merged with another Lia Sophia, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the other company.

_**In Response to Legal Process**_. We also may disclose the information we collect from you in order to comply with the law, a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena.

_**To Protect Us and Others**_. We also may disclose the information we collect from you where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use or this Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which Lia Sophia is involved.

_**Aggregate and De-Identified Information**_. We may share aggregate or de-identified information about users with third parties for marketing, advertising, research or similar purposes.

**Cookies and Other Tracking**

As mentioned above, we might use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Site or Services. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you.

_**Do-Not-Track.**_ Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies or opting out of ad networks).

_**Cookies.**_ Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. We might use cookies to uniquely identify you, in order to help us to process your transactions and requests, to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity, and to display advertising both on our Site and on third-party sites. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you disable cookies some features of our Site may not function.

_**Clear GIFs**_. Clear GIFs (a.k.a. web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, though, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages, not stored on your hard drive. We might use clear GIFs to track the activities of Site visitors and App users, help us manage content, and compile statistics about usage. We and our third party service providers also might use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded.

_**Third-Party Analytics**_. We also use automated devices and applications, such as [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), to evaluate usage of our Sites and the Services we provide. We use these tools to gather safe information about users to help us improve our services, performance and user experiences. These analytics providers may use cookies and other technologies to perform their services, and may combine the information that they collect about you on our Sites with other information that they have collected. This Policy does not cover such third parties’ use of the data.

**Marketing Choices**

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us

**Plug-ins and Social Media Widgets**

Our Site may include social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook Like button and the "Share this" button, as well as other interactive mini-programs that run on our Site and Services and enable certain features to work (e.g., blogs and comments). These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly and for purposes. These features are displayed on our Site, but are hosted by third parties, and are subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

**Third-Party Ad Networks**

We use third parties such as ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services (“Ad Networks”) to display advertisements on our Sites, to assist us in displaying advertisements on third party websites, and to evaluate the success of our advertising campaigns. Ad Networks display advertisements based on your visits to our Site as well as other websites. This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements by displaying ads for products and services in which you might be interested. Ad Networks may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third party cookies and other technologies are governed by each Ad Network’s privacy policy, not this one. We may provide these third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and our services, as well as aggregate or non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our Site and users of our service.

You may opt-out of many Ad Networks, including those operated by members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). For more information regarding this practice by NAI members, and your choices regarding these Ad Networks, please visit the NAI websites [www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

Opting out of one or more NAI member Ad Networks only means that those members no longer will deliver targeted content or ads to you, based on your visits to multiple websites. It does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content or ads on our Site or other websites. Additional information is available on NAI’s and DAA’s websites accessible by the above links.

**User Generated Content**

We invite you to post content on our Site, including your comments, pictures, and any other information that you would like to be available on our Site. If you post content to our Site, all of the information that you post will be available to all visitors to our Site. If you post your own content on our Site or Services, your posting may become public and Lia Sophia cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Policy, the law, or your personal privacy.

**Location**

We are based in the United States, and our service providers may be located in the United States or various other jurisdictions. You acknowledge that your personal information may be processed and stored in foreign jurisdictions and that the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies in those jurisdictions may be able to obtain disclosure of that personal information through the laws of the foreign jurisdiction.

**Third-Party Links**

Our Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites. Any access to and use of such linked websites is not governed by this Policy, but instead is governed by the privacy policies of those third party websites. We are not responsible for the information practices of such third party websites.

**Security of My Personal Information**

We have implemented measures to protect the information we collect. Please be aware that no data security measures can guarantee 100% security. You should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your password, phone, and computer by, among other things, signing off after using a shared computer, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess, and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.

**Access To My Personal Information**

You may modify your account profile and review previous orders by logging into your account and updating your profile information, or by contacting us at [LSOutlet@liasophia.com](mailto:LSOutlet@liasophia.com). Please note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Site for a period of time, and we maintain a copy of such information as part of our business records. You may also request that we change personal information that you cannot access directly that is inaccurate or incomplete.

**What Choices Do I Have Regarding Use of My Personal Information?**

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained in the e-mail, or by emailing us at [LSOutlet@liasophia.com](mailto:LSOutlet@liasophia.com). Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you e-mails about your account or any Services you have requested or received from us.

**Children Under 13**

Our Services are not designed for children under 13. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our systems.

**Special Information for California Consumers; California Privacy Rights**

California residents may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personally identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: [LSOutlet@liasophia.com](mailto:LSOutlet@liasophia.com). Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our Services or would like to make a complaint, please contact us at [LSOutlet@liasophia.com](mailto:LSOutlet@liasophia.com).

**Changes to this Policy**

This Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Policy on our Site, at https://www.liasophia.com/privacy-policy. If we make any changes to this Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on our Site, or emailing your email address of record.
